<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AOT Wallpaper</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="nav_open">Open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close</string>


    <!-- res/values/strings.xml -->

    <string name="about_us_content">
        <![CDATA[
        <h1> About Us </h1>
        Welcome to the Attack on Titan Wallpaper App by Lyka Apps!<br><br>

        At Lyka Apps, we are passionate about bringing you the best mobile experiences. Our Attack on Titan Wallpaper App is dedicated to all the fans of this incredible anime series, offering a vast collection of high-quality wallpapers that capture the essence of the Titans, the Survey Corps, and the gripping world of Attack on Titan.<br><br>

        Our Vision<br><br>

        We understand the importance of personalizing your device to reflect your interests and fandoms. Our vision is to provide a seamless and visually stunning experience for Attack on Titan enthusiasts, allowing you to adorn your screens with captivating wallpapers that pay homage to the epic storytelling and iconic characters of this beloved anime.<br><br>

        Features<br><br>

        - Extensive Wallpaper Collection: Immerse yourself in our curated selection of Attack on Titan wallpapers, featuring breathtaking scenes, character portraits, and iconic moments from the series.<br>
        - High-Quality Images: Every wallpaper is meticulously chosen and optimized for high resolution, ensuring crisp and vivid visuals on your device.<br>
        - User-Friendly Interface: Our app is designed with you in mind. Navigate effortlessly through the app, preview wallpapers, and set your favorites as backgrounds with just a few taps.<br><br>

        Copyright Notice<br><br>

        The wallpapers featured in this app are sourced from various platforms, including user submissions. We make every effort to respect copyright and intellectual property rights. If you believe that any content within our app infringes on your copyright, please contact us immediately.<br><br>

        About Lyka Apps<br><br>

        Lyka Apps is a dedicated mobile application development team committed to delivering top-notch apps that cater to diverse interests. As the publisher of the Attack on Titan Wallpaper App, we take pride in creating a platform that allows fans to express their love for the series through their device screens.<br><br>

        Connect With Us<br><br>

        We value your feedback and suggestions. If you have any questions, concerns, or if there/s anything specific you/d like to see in our app, please don/t hesitate to reach out.<br>
        Email: lykaappshelp@gmail.com
       <br><br>

        Thank you for choosing the Attack on Titan Wallpaper App by Lyka Apps. We hope you enjoy the wallpapers, and if you have any copyright concerns, please email us immediately.<br><br>

        Happy wallpapering!<br><br>

        Lyka Apps Team
        ]]>
    </string>


</resources>